敦V播:法人致其同胞的公告
London calling, with Frenchmen speaking to their countrymen.
(法S陷^)
(第二次世界大鸬谖迥)
看啊,多N尤说雒妗…
Take a look at that. What a handsome sight...
……第三帝的傲
...the pride of the Third Reich.
勇敢的中士送咖啡o╊^炮兵
The brave sergeant taking coffee to the beachgunners.
@就是iM眼中高等民族的一例C
So that's a sample of the master race in a pig's eye.
(德西司令 T・德施泰特元)
(法卡昂地^抵抗M成T 伊妮恩・波伊塔)
怎N回事？
What's going on here?
(Ｔr.Ｖ.ＰＩ.Ｐ－要塞指]部)
(}米伊格Y斯L v山大・雷Z)
在@黑暗的r刻,在@黑暗的夜Y……
In this darkest hour, in the gloom of night...
……我]必要^望
...we must not despair.
(皮・路易斯・_m德)
我要保持我最初的信念,远ú灰!
Let us keep our faith intact,unswerving!
榱宋每人……
For each of us...
……自由正在砼R
...deliverance is coming.
(沃{・普拉斯P少校)
(德第三五二海防)
我要在整海岸布下地雷和障K物
We need mines and obstacles along the whole coast.
包括每一海,每一沙丘……
At every beach, on every dune...
……每一K礁石
...on every rock.
已阎昧硕嗌伲
How many have been installed?
四百f,元
Four million, Herr Field Marshal.
五月必_到六百f
-
It has to be six million by May.
德西Ｂ集F群司令 埃亍ぢ∶元
-Six million.-Our men are constantly deployed.
－六百f－我的人一刻未停
根本]有提及休整的事(德第十五集F司令 　h斯・T・_穆特上)
There's no point in even discussing rest.
－部已精疲力竭了－H鄣鸟T・_穆特……
-The troops are completely exhausted.-My dear Herr von Salmuth...
……你更意你的部下……
...which would your troops rather be...
……筋疲力M是拭？
...exhausted or dead?
看看@,各位
Just look at it, gentlemen.
如此o和
How calm, how peaceful it is.
M在英和W之g的@片水域……
A strip of water between England and the Continent...
……盟和我各一方
...between the Allies and us.
但是在那^平o的地平上,伏著一^怪F
But beyond that peaceful horizon, a monster waits.
整b待l的部,,和wC……
A coiled spring of men, ships and planes...
……想要一e⑽
...straining to be released against us.
但]有一名盟士兵能登上@片海
But not a single Allied soldier shall reach the shore.
]有一名盎格美利匀四苌孀氵@片海
Not a single Anglo-American shall set foot on the beaches.
o@次入侵碜院r何地……
Whenever or wherever this invasion may come, gentlemen...
……我都耻缭诤０哆
...I shall destroy the enemy there, at the water's edge.
相信我,各位
Believe me, gentlemen.
入侵的^二十四小r⒊殛PI
The first 24 hours of the invasion will be decisive.
於盟和我碚f,都⑹亲盥L的一天……
For the Allies as well as the Germans,
it will be the longest day...
……最漫L的一天
...the longest day.
最L的一天
德西司令部⒅\L 瑟・布T特Y特少
德西司令部 法巴黎郊^
－魏(Paul Verlaine)的？－是的,第一(《秋歌》)
-The poem by Verlaine?-Yes, the first verse.
倒回重放!
Play it back!
安o!
Silence!
(德第十五集F反gL 海默斯・梅耶中校)
敦V播:
法人致其同胞的公告
Frenchmen speaking to their countrymen.
@是一些c人有P的口信
Here are some personal messages.
「秋天的小提琴那LL的柩省
"The long sobs of the violins of autumn. "
重}
I repeat:
「秋天的小提琴那LL的柩省
"The long sobs of the violins of autumn. "
有]有通知所有指]部？
Have you notified all commands?
如果柏林方面是Φ,那我截到第二r……
If Berlin is right, when we intercept the second verse...
……就表示入侵⒃诙十四小r劝l
...it will mean the invasion will come within 24 hours.
o我看看第二
Give me the text of the second verse.
「用握
"Wounds my heart with a monotonous languor."
去年我截了狄园儆的信息,狄园儆!
We've intercepted hundreds of messages in the last year, hundreds!
我一而再再而三地下令戒
I've ordered alerts again and again.
槭颤N@首比其他信息有更多意味？
Why should this poem mean more than other messages?
告V我
Tell me this:
它提供任何耻何r何地入侵的索幔
Does it give us any clue as to where they will land and when?
然不
Of course it doesn't.
有五十f由我指]
I have half a million men under my command.
如果我不嘞铝罱涞脑,如何S持o……
How can I maintain discipline if I keep my troops on the alert...
……就因榘亓忠ι倒辖芈到的一首？
...just because a pair of nitwits in Berlin intercept a poem?
不,布T特Y特,不用戒
No, Blumentritt, no alert.
尤其是在@N天
And especially not in this weather.
－有事幔浚]有,L官
-Anything else?-No, sir.
早,元
Good morning, field marshal.
－有情r幔浚]有什N要o的情r
-Any news?-Nothing important.
昨天下午加R遭到了Z炸
Fighter bombers hit the Pas-de-Calais yesterday afternoon.
昨晚]l生其他事,L暴要砹
Nothing much happened last night. The storm.
我P心的只是今早@鲲L暴
That's all I'm interested in this morning, the storm.
不知哪淼,把我的玫瑰都吹牧
It came from nowhere, blew my roses to bits.
海
There are 5-foot waves in the Channel...
……L速每小r三十到四十英里
...and winds of 30 to 40 miles per hour.
以六月而言……
For the month of June...
……是二十年碜毫拥暮
...it's the worst Channel storm in 20 years.
我到希特斯加登x元首的事怎N恿耍
My appointment at Berchtesgaden?
s德④今天要去元首……
General Jodl will see the Fuhrer today...
……K槟安排x
...and confirm the appointment for you.
您是要按去回德幔
Will you still go to Germany as planned?
能找到更好的rg幔
Can you think of a better time?
@N天饪硪持m到下星期
The weather is expected to continue like this for another week.
英
盟一千一百零八座I之一
快跟上,下一
Snap it up. Jerk the lead.
又要我吃@玩意？
You expect us to eat this slop again?
我才不管你吃不吃,老兄
I don't care what you do with it, mac.
不想吃,扔掉好了
Eat it, throw it out.
我靠做@拿薪水
I get paid for cooking it.
得了,添上吧
Come on. Put it on.
快跟上
Snap it up.
下一
Jerk the lead.
你]睡X幔
Didn't you get any sleep?
_玩笑,自打磉@我就]睡^
Are you kidding? I haven't slept since we got here.
我得到_切消息
I got the absolute lowdown.
就在今晚,是真的
It's on for tonight. For sure.
是幔
Yeah.
我和ＦB一砘S骰子rf的
I got in this crap game with this guy from F Company.
－他是④的髁畋－快,快
-He's an orderly for some general.-Move it. Move it.
嘿,哈奇
Hey, Hutchy!
哈奇,我有事要你
Hutchy, I want to ask you something.
嘿,哈奇森……
Hey, Hutchinson...
……如果是重要行,我信回家幔
...do you think they'd let me writehome?If it was really important?
不可能,夥,得保密
Not likely, mate. Security.
老丘吉K不相信我
I don't think old Churchill trusts us.
是o我太太,她快生了
It's the wife, you see. She's going to have a baby.
第一孩子，是吧？
Your first, is it?
不是我的,但我很心她
Oh, it's not mine, but I'm dead worried about her.
她身w不是很好
She's not too strong, you see.
老兄,那赫娉
Man, that stink.
有柴油,Rr所,I吐物
Diesel oil, backed-up toilets, vomit.
]有地方安置病
And there ain't no place left to get sick in.
I吐袋都M了
The puke bags is full.
消防桶也吐M了
The fire buckets is full.
只剩下盔能用
All we got left is our helmets.
六月
June.
我老^子每年六月是我去露I……
Every June my old man used to take me camping...
……在
...up in the Blue Mountains.
我整天都打C~
We'd hunt and fish all day long.
到了晚上……
And at night...
……我就睡在星光之下
...we'd sleep out under the stars.
B毛毯都不用
Didn't even need a blanket.
六月
June.
又是L,又是雨
Wind and rain. Wind and rain.
有完]完？
Don't it ever stop?
看,老爹,我只想著出l
Look, Dad, all I want to do is get going.
管它L是雨,哪怕降落在艾菲F塔上都行
Wind or no wind. Even if we land in Paris on the Eiffel Tower.
－想想看……－中校找我
-Come to think of it---Colonel wants us.
所有人
All of us.
第五○五F第二IIL 本苊鳌し兜衔痔刂行
美第八十二空降
我接到通知,有
I've notified the adjutant, change in schedule.
今天碰^之後……
After briefing session today...
……所有部都要⑴c地面作咽
...all troops will participate in ground tactics and deployment.
在@N天,^？
In this weather, sir?
然,哈丁,你能保C降落在法r……
Of course, Harding,if you can ensure that we'll land in France...
－……是大晴天幔浚我不是@意思
-...in sunshine and dry weather.-Didn't mean that.
－那是什N意思？－不是指天
-What did you mean?-It isn't the weather.
是等待rg,大伙都等不及了
It's the waiting. These men are itching to go.
我想用不著我硖嵝涯恪…
I don't think I have to remind you...
……@已持m⒔五年了
...that this war has been going on for almost five years.
半W洲遭到侵
Half of Europe has been overrun and occupied.
我是凫缎淼
We're comparative newcomers.
英囊痪潘摹鹉昶鹁鸵恢泵媾R入侵，如芒在背
England's gone through a blitz with a knife at her throat since 1940.
我相信他也迫不及待地想要反攻
I am quite sure that they too are impatient and itching to go.
f得蚯宄了幔
Do I make myself clear?
是的,^,很清楚
Yes, sir. Quite clear.
有三百f人v在@u上
Three million men penned up on this island.
像@拥谋I遍及整英格m
All over England, in staging areas like this.
我正在有史以碜钪匾r刻的前沿
We're on the threshold of the most crucial day of our times.
三百f人在@……
Three million men out there...
……蓄荽l,就榱诉@一刻
...keyed up, and waiting for that big step-off.
H上不止是他
They aren't exactly alone.
通知部,下午二c前收拾好行b
Notify the men. Full packs and equipment, 1400 hours.
是,^
Yes, sir.
他f都能派上用
－
They said they have both issues available.
美第二十九步兵副L Z曼・Ｄ・科塔准
他f都能派上用
(美第二十九步兵副L Z曼・Ｄ・科塔准)
我更喜g@一款,比^
I prefer this type. It allows you more freedom.
登後起肀容^快
Quicker to get rid of when we hit the beach.
－怎N樱浚定下砹
-Well?-It's on.
今晚,照M行
Tonight, as scheduled.
－只要天獠桓糟－能更糟幔
-If the weather isn't worse.-How worse can it get?
艾克召集高釉诰劈c三十_
Ike has called a high-level conference for 9:30.
我不是艾森豪威,我是副L
I am not Eisenhower. I am an assistant division commander.
我什N都不管,但他不能再取消
I don't know from nothing, but he can't call it off again.
弗m克,P掉那玩意
Frank, turn that thing off.
四千艘船都已b浜
Four thousand ships loaded for bear.
部做好了出l
Troops ready to go.
一f一千架wC在Sr待命
Eleven thousand planes on the line.
加上一f八千惚和天知道有多少的滑翔C
Eighteen thousand paratroopers.God only knows how many gliders.
Z,放c
Norm, relax.
皇家空f大LSr可能停止
RAF says the gale can stop as suddenly as it began.
所以他前天昨天都@Nξf
So they told us yesterday and the day before.
Z
Look, Norm.
我所有人……
We're all of us just as...
……都和你一优沃_始行
...dedicated to this thing as you are,just as anxious to get going.
也包括艾克
And that includes Ike.
如果他再次取消行,一定有他的理由
Now if he calls it off again, he knows what he's doing.
他然有理由,@我知道
Of course he does. I know that.
我考]的是突舨筷,一共二十f人……
I'm just thinking about those assault troops.200,000 of them...
……呆在船上,恐怕吐得七八素了
...out there on those ships. They're probably seasick as hell.
有些人在「澡盆子」Y呆了都快三天了
Some of those men have been on those tubs for almost three days.
行影
I say go.
行,管它天獠惶
Go. Weather or no weather.
不!
No!
我押一百!戆
A hundred on the bone! Let's go.
－o我五十K,我光了－我手庖膊辉觞N
-Hey, give me 50 bucks. I'm busted.-I'm not doing so good myself.
借我五十K行幔
Hey, lend me 50 bucks?
－借我二十K行幔浚去死吧
-Lend me 20 bucks?-Drop dead.
借我十K行幔
Lend me 10?
－五十K一注－我有
-Fifty on a bet.-I got it.
一,二,三,四,五
One, two, three, four, five.
五十!
Fifty!
我,我
Let me hear it, let me hear it.
－五和二,四和三－六!@硬β!
-Five and two, four and three.-Six! That's the way we go!
一直是七c的,邪T,真邪T
Seven points in a row.It ain't logical, it just ain't logical.
－@把押一百K－一百K,再加二十
-There's 100 out there.-A hundred dollars, $20.
有要押幔
Anything open?
－再硭氖－再硭氖
-Forty more.-Forty more.
你有注了
You got a bet.
－好了,你他……－等等,等一下
-Okay, you mother-loving-Just a minute. Wait a minute.
拿著,用@
Here you are. Use this.
－你不以椤…－]什N以
-You don't think l'd---I don't think anything.
我只是想到杯子l出的音
I just like to hear the sound when it comes out of the cup.
就@,u吧
That's it. Shake it.
好了,我看看你的\,,_吧
Okay. Let me see what you do with it now.  Go ahead. Shoot.
－是什N？
－]什N
-What is it?
-Nothing.
－七!－正是我想要的!
-Seven!-That's what I wanted!
是l拿@杯子淼模
Who put this cup in the game?
－下一把,lS？－我押一百K
-Next shooter. Who's coming up?-I'll go $100.
他下一百,有l接P？
He's shooting 100.Who's got it?
－看好你的注－一百K
-Watch your side bets.-A hundred dollars.
有我的信,舒茨的？
You got a letter for me. Schultz, huh?
有,在@
Yeah, that's it.
xx,夥
Thanks, buddy.
－你A了多少？－不多,才汕五多一c
-How much did you take him for?-Not much. Just a hair over 2500.
－汕五？－
-Twenty-five hundred?-Yeah.
哦,夥,汕五？
Oh, man, 2500?
F在AX可不太妙
It's too bad you had to win it now.
「F在」是什N意思？
What do you mean, now?
要是今晚行幽隳眠@些有什N用？
Suppose we take off tonight.  What will you do with it?
五百K用碓诎屠韬染婆蓠R子
Five I take with me to Paris to blow on the broads and wine.
一千K留在@等回碓倩
A thou I leave here for seed when I get back.
剩下的寄o我
And the rest I send to my mother.
哦,夥,汕五,有巴黎
Oh, man, 2500. And in Paris.
你@N好\
You always was lucky.
得在布拉格堡那晚幔
Hey, remember that night in Fort Bragg?
得
I remember it.
知道,我想我^去o自己粕弦话
You know, I think I sneak over there and give it a big whang myself.
致锊荒兀]什N可的嘛？
Why not? What's to lose?
死
Damn it.
他致锾岵祭格堡？
Why did he have to mention Fort Bragg?
那次S骰子我手夂芎
I was lucky, all right, in that crap game.
第二天空降就把腿弄嗔
Next day I break my leg in a jump.
做了月恳
And two months in traction.
汕五百美元
Twenty-five hundred dollars.
我@子]有^@N多X
That's more money I ever had in my whole life.
我知道
I know.
夥,我知道
Man, I just know.
我倒想知道掉汕五百美元要多久
I wonder how long it takes to lose $2500.
英皇家空痿YCw行T 大l・坎空中尉
硪槐,特德
Pint of sludge, Ted.
你好,戴夫,看到s翰尼]有？
Oh, hello, Dave. Hey, you seen Johnny?
有
Yes.
他在哪？
Well, where is he?
f啊,戴夫
Come on, Dave.
他借走了我的靴子
I need my boots. Johnny's borrowed them.
他在哪？
Where is he?
躺在……
At the bottom...
……海底
...of the Channel.
你是f……
You mean...
……他死了？
...he's bought it?
在加R中了高射炮
Ack-ack over Calais.
他跳了出,可降落]能打_
He jumped clean, ut his parachute didn't open.
@中只乘下你了,戴夫
That leaves just you in the squadron, Dave.
我是指一九四○年那一芾媳
I mean, of the old 1940 mob.
我@批人越越少，正是我一直心的事情之一
What's always worried me about being one of the few is the way we keep on getting fewer.
可z的老s翰尼
Poor old Johnny.
\庹嬖,在@口
Bad luck, it happening now.
－@口？有什N^e？－他和你一愚哌^了不列鹨!
-Now, then. What's the difference?-He went through the Battle of Britain just like you!
要是今晚好蛏觥…
And now if the big show starts tonight...
……他就不能加入
...he won't be in it.
不要再提他好幔
Look, will you please shut up about him?
好的好的,Σ黄,Σ黄
All right, all right. I'm sorry, I'm sorry.
f今晚的事]有？
You heard something about tonight?
不,]有,什N都]到
No, no. I haven't heard anything.
－那你才f的是什N？－@,只是…….
-What are you talking about then?-Well, it's just....
－^m,^m－我有NA感就是在今晚
-Go on, go on.-I have a feeling it's on for tonight.
－如此而已－A感
-That's all.-A feeling.
е你的A感去e吧
Take your feeling somewhere else.
我得封信
I've got a letter to write.
我脑缟掀r就有@NA感
I've had this feeling since I woke up.
整天都有@N感X
I've had it with me all day long.
o法[它
I can't shake it off.
就是今晚,我知道@一c
It's tonight. I know it is.
好吧,就是今晚
All right, it's tonight.
正合我意
Suits me fine.
今晚,今天下午,F在!
Tonight. This afternoon. Now!
我是f……
I mean...
……在我喝完啤酒之後
...as soon as I finish this beer.
－④,你F在有空幔浚M戆
-General, can you spare me a minute?-Come in.
－xx－要咖啡幔
-Thank you.-Can I get you coffee?
－不用,xx－我可得睃c
-No, thanks.-I'll get some for myself.
美第八十二空降副L 詹姆斯・Ｍ・加文准
在下雨幔
Is it still raining?
下下停停,停停下下
On and off, off and on.
有r我想知道上帝究竟站在哪一
Sometimes I wonder which side God's on.
什N？
What?
我f,有r我想知道上帝站在哪一
I say, sometimes I wonder which side God's on.
好}
Good question.
你有何想法,范？
What's on your mind, Van?
我心我降落地c的安排
I'm concerned about the placement of our drop zones.
^mf
Go on.
我知道F在提出新方案太晚了c……
I know this is a hell of a late date to bring up something new...
……但你o我出了y}
...but you've given me a tough nut to crack.
－我越想越X得棘手－我知道,范
-It gets tougher every time I try.-I know, Van.
}米伊格Y斯，座落在德唯一能用怼…
Sainte-Mere-Eglise straddles the only road the Germans can use...
……打入我北翼的公路上,我必拿下
...to drive into our northern flank. But it has to be taken.
而且必守住
And it has to be held.
所以我才要你去,范
That's why I gave you the job, Van.
－能用下黑板幔浚然
-Can I use your board?-Of course.
@是那,有重兵把守
Here's the town. Heavily fortified.
@是沼傻,德已引水淹]
Down here is the swamp area that the Germans have flooded.
@二者中g，距小四英里是我的著c
And in between, four miles from the town, is our drop zone.
如果出了差e而提前著……
Now, if anything goes wrong and we undershoot...
……降落在沼傻鼐陷入困境
...we land in this flooded area and are bogged down.
如果w^^了,就像泥一勇湎隆…
If we overshoot, we come down like clay pigeons...
……直接面碜孕℃的火力
...smack dab in the center of Sainte-Mere-Eglise.
所以我在附近的村子士兵低空跳
That's why I gave the men training in low-level jumps near the villages.
我f了
So I've heard.
我收到了碜载克斯荷市h的投V
Got a complaint from the city council at Bexhall.
你的一些部下因w^^而降落在市^
Some of your men overshot the drop zone
and landed in the town.
－阻K交通_一小r－]e,^,我也在那
-Tied up traffic for an hour.-That's true, sir. I was with them.
遭遇蕊L,⑽吹^了渖摇…
Sudden crosswind hit us, swept us over the treetops...
……大家都o吹散了
...scattered us all over the place.
－你落在了哪？－落在一家女修道院的院子Y
-Where did you end up?-In the courtyard of a convent.
放c,范,坐吧
Relax, Van. Sit down.
月砦都吃M了苦^
The last few months have been a tough grind on all of us.
我f你和你的部下一直在刻苦
I hear you've been working yourself and your battalion hard.
缀]停^
Almost without a stop.
F在我就要_始行恿恕…
Now that we're almost at the end of the line...
……你致锊蛔自己和部下放一下
...why don't you try easing up on yourself and on the men?
偶放一下能部的B更好
Sometimes a battalion can be sharpened to too fine a point.
有r指]官也一
Sometimes a commander can too.
Well
如果行永^m延後的
if there's any further delay
我求允S重新安排降落地c
I request permission to submit a new placement for our drop zones.
行,蟾姘
All right. Put it in writing.
搞正式一c,@是你的
Make it official. That's your prerogative.
不^艾克今晚要在_S克大钦匍_一Qh
(_S克大恰―盟海司令部,位於愦蚊┧钩峭)
But Ike has called a final meeting
for tonight at Southwick House.
如果通^了,今晚九c三十就要出l
If it's on, we'll get the green light by 9:30.
－可能性有多大？
－超^五成
-What are the chances?
-Better than 50-50.
我什N也]f,④。我有@最好的一I……
Forget everything I said. I got the best battalion in this division...
而且已渚途w
and they're ready.
英皇家空首席庀箢 Ｊ・Ｎ・斯塔格空上校
砹,最新的蟾
Here it is. The latest report.
－_S克大(盟海司令部)打淼,L官－我是斯塔格
-It's Southwick House, sir.-Stagg here.
是的,L官,新h的移颖阮A期的要快
Yes, sir. The new front's moving in much faster than we thought.
是的,很明@有所改善
Yes, sir, it's definitely improving.
我到的,L官,九c三十
I'll be there, sir. 9:30.
－要茶,L官？－咖啡吧,庖稽c
-Would you like some more tea, sir?-Coffee, and make it black.
xx
Please.
等等,普Y勒中校
One moment, Colonel Priller.
他槭颤N]受法治？
Why wasn't he court-martialed?
他打下了一百三十二架wC
He shot down 132 planes.
(德空西部 沃夫・海格空中)
你好,「匹普斯」老夥
Hello, Pips, old boy.
德空第二十六痿YCLs瑟夫・普Y勒中校
共袈湟话倭阋患茱wC,其中四引擎Z炸C十一架
e叫我「匹普斯」老夥
Don't call me "Pips, old boy."
我在Kr你就是糟糕的w行T
You were a rotten pilot when we flew in Russia.
你F在官了,可仍然是糟糕的w行T
You're flying a desk now, but you're still a rotten pilot!
你@是什N？
What's that you're saying?
我C在@右鬼的C觥…
I'm squatting here on this God-forsaken airfield...
……就杉茱wC,粹是啥哑
...with only two planes, two stinking crates!
然,你的命令倒是生效了
Oh, sure, sure, your orders were followed!
可我的中天知道在哪!
Now my squadrons are God-knows-where!
oB早就]了,我F在做什N？
My supplies are all gone. What am I supposed to do now?
但是「匹普斯」,我必分散w行中,必!
But Pips, we had to disperse our fighter squadrons. We had to!
看看我加R附近的C鲈馐芰耸颤N!
Look what happened to our airstrips around the Pas-de-Calais!
@N主意真是愚蠢之O!
The whole idea is absolutely idiotic!
你不我前M反而我後退
You move us back instead of forward!
然,我知道天毫,所以他不一定M攻
Sure, I know the weather's lousy and they probably won't invade...
……但f一他M攻怎Nk？
...but what would happen if they did?
你t解以我的b渲辽僖商觳拍苴s到
But you know I can't get there with my equipment for two days.
老f,你全都了!
I tell you, you're all crazy!
普Y勒是@N急躁……
Priller has always been a hothead...
……但不要因此而p他
...but let's not underestimate him.
他的不o道理
What he says is not entirely illogical.
天蟾嬖觞Nf？
What's the weather report?
整海
Slightly better over the Channel.
我想不有意外,即使……
I wouldn't be surprised if--
－下次天蟾媸颤Nr候到？－今晚八c,④
-When's the next weather report?-Tonight at 8, general.
Sr向我蟾嫣馇r
Keep me posted on the weather.
替我好晚餐座位]有？
You made my dinner reservations?
好了,④
Yes, I did, general.
全部取消
Cancel everything.
－拿了]有？－拿了,L官
-Have you got them?-Yes, sir.
o我
Let me have them.
是送o我太太的鞋,特地在巴黎做的……
Shoes for my wife, I had them specially made in Paris...
……樗c祝生日,就是明天,六月六
...for her birthday, tomorrow, the sixth of June.
代我祝她生日快
Please wish her a happy birthday.
xx,斯派_
Thank you, Speidel.
他致锊辉谖逶逻M攻？ 那N理想的天狻…
Why didn't they attack in May? The weather was perfect....
潮汐都很正常,可F在…….
Tides were right, and now....
F在M攻就得Dy了
An attack now would be embarrassing.
_, 但我用不著心
Let's go. But I don't think we need worry.
(德西Ｂ集F群⒅\L h斯・斯派_博士少)
(eO⑴c推翻希特勒密\活K窟B到隆美)
(疳,於1957年出任北s地面部司令)
(德第七集F第八十四L 埃Y奇・R克斯中)
浜昧,L官？
Is the plan ready, sir?
是的,好了
Yes, yes, quite finished.
鹌逋蒲荨…
War games...
……理性的入侵
...theoretical invasions.
s去雷恩只是榱嗽谏潮P上插些小旗T了
Rush to Rennes just to push little flags around a table.
中的[!
Playing at war!
您是A是,L官？
Do you win or lose, sir?
我^幔
Have I ever lost?
但是④,@次您扮演的是艾森豪威
But general, this time you play the role of Eisenhower.
我A是因槲也依常行事
I win because I go against the rules.
A料中橙暮
We expect them to cross at the narrowest part of the Channel...
……而且是在好天,但^於@而易
...and in good weather. But that's too simple, too obvious.
我x的是最之,在最毫拥奶,M攻此地
I choose the widest part, in the worst weather,and attack here.
Z曼底
In Normandy.
在毫犹庵中
And in bad weather!
例如F在……
Like now...
……@N奶
...bad weather!
要作出判嗪芾щy
Trying to pick a trend is difficult.
庀蠼嵌碚f,目前的情形直像是寒冬
From a meteorological standpoint,conditions almost resemble mid-winter.
至於Z曼底
And Normandy?
L,,以及F饣\罩著整海
High winds, clouds, and some fog over the beaches.
不管怎,我能完全肯定的是……
However, I can say with a certain degree of safety...
……⒂幸欢味rg的好天
...that we can expect a brief period of fair conditions.
那NQ而言之
Let me summarize, then.
你能保C的就是⒂幸欢O槎旱暮锰
What you're promising us is a barely tolerable period of fair conditions.
是不是@樱
Am I right?
是的
Yes.
@拥l件hh低於最低要求
Conditions that are far below the minimum requirements.
我只能保C@些
That's all I can promise.
你M力了,斯塔格,xx
You've done your best, Stagg. Thank you, gentlemen.
那N,情r就是……
Well, there it is.
我已⑦M攻推t^一次
We've postponed the attack once already.
F在,要N趁六的最低l件l舆M攻……
Now, either we go on the sixth,with only marginal conditions...
……要N再次延後……
...or postpone again...
……等待理想的夂l件
...in the hope of getting perfect conditions.
你X得怎,蒙蒂？
What do you think, Monty?
我x襁M攻,M攻
I say, go. Go.
我必提醒各位……
I must remind everybody...
M攻「WR哈海」和「q他海」的美船
that the American convoy for the Omaha and Utah beaches
行程最h
they've farthest to go
必在半小r以认蛩下令
must be given the order within the next half-hour
……如果突u安排在六的
...if the assault is to take place on the sixth.
我不能⒔二十五f人一直呆在船上
We can't keep almost a quarter of a million men on ships
o限期地待命
in embarkation areas, indefinitely.
我等得越久,安全[患就越多
The longer we wait, the more acute our security problem.
下一次
The next time
潮汐和月亮的正常出F
the tides and the moon will be right
七月以前不有
Not before July.
各位……
Gentlemen...
延後如此之久
such a postponement
是非常痛苦的x
is too bitter to contemplate
^妙的,④,不合常,但堪Q^妙
A brilliant plan, general. Unorthodox, but brilliant.
好在@只是[
Fortunately, it's only a game.
我X得不用太心
I don't think we have much to worry about.
艾森豪威聿桓颐半U
Eisenhower would never take the gamble.
聿
Never.
我十分肯定下令行
I'm quite positive we must give the order.
管不意
I don't like it
但只能@
but there it is
各位
Gentlemen
除了行游铱床怀鲇衅渌x
I don't see how we can possibly do anything else but go.
我是威d
Wilson speaking.
是,L官
Yes, sir.
定了,是艾克下的Q定,今晚,按行
It's on, sir. Ike's made the decision. Tonight, as scheduled!
我是姆森上校
Colonel Tomson speaking.
xx
Thank you.
下一站……
Next stop...
……Z曼底
...Normandy.
上帝保佑
God help us now.
(英第一特N突袈 拉瓦特炀)
我是拉瓦特
Lovat here.
各位……
Gentlemen...
……我等待的日子K於砹
...the day we've been waiting for has arrived.
M攻!我出l
Invasion! We're on our way.
④
General.
(美第四步兵L 雷蒙德・巴D少)
收到命令了,行
The orders have been given. It's on.
召集指]官到官室_
Have the battalion commanders join me in the wardroom.
行了,中士
All right, sergeant.
你是我空降的眼睛
You men are the eyes of our airborne Army.
作惚引T,你只有一任
You, the pathfinders, will have one job, and one job only:
惚部指明降落地c
To light the drop zones for our paratroops.
加上英人和加拿大人,你⑹恰…
Along with the British and Canadians you'll be the first men...
……第一批登法的人,住:
...to land in France.  And remember this:
到_Z曼底之後……
When you get to Normandy...
……你⒅挥幸朋友
...you'll only have one friend:
上帝
God.
有@
And this.
@……
This...
……是珀特
...is Rupert.
F在,我要Ⅳ珀特……
Now, we are going to drop Rupert...
……和很多似他的同伴……
...and a lot more like him...
……空投至耻後方
...behind the invasion area.
他……
He's...
……是非常特e的同伴,珀特
...a very extraordinary fellow, Rupert.
他可以f是……
He's a sort of...
……一支伪部
...one-man army, all by himself.
我做o你看
Let me show you.
你看看珀特著後l生什N事
Let me show you what happens when Rupert hits the ground.
中士,把絷P掉
Sergeant, switch off the lights, please.
好了,中士,行了
All right, sergeant, that's all.
好的,蛄,o
All right, come on. Simmer down.
行了,起戆
Come on, up.
珀特和他的弟兄可以Φ人做同拥氖
It's possible that Rupert and his men will do the same thing to the Germans.
迷惑他,他心後方
Confuse them, make them look over their shoulders
……向e`的方向l起攻
...and launch an attack in the wrong direction.
立正!
Ten-hut!
－「蟋蟀」已分l下去－我到了
-The crickets have been distributed.-So I heard.
稍息!
At ease!
大家已作好了
You're as ready as we can make you.
@五分X的玩具……
This five-cent toy...
……不是榱俗你l笑
...wasn't issued to you for laughs.
它也S能保住你的命
It may save your life.
你⒃诤诎抵兄
You're gonna be landing in the dark.
在h笆背面的人未必和你穿著相同的制服,所以……
On the other side of that hedgerow...
...the fellow may not be wearing the same uniform you are. So...
一「卡嗒」
one click
……要以陕「卡嗒」作榛
...is to be answered by two clicks.
如果你]收到回……
And if you don't get that answering click...
……趴下,然後_火
...hit the dirt and open fire.
重}一次:
I repeat:
一「卡嗒」……
One click...
……必以陕「卡嗒」作榛
...must be answered by two clicks.
F在,保管好@玩意,它和你的武器一又匾
Now, hang on to this gimmick.It's as important as your weapon.
－懂]有？－清楚明t,^
-Do you read me?-Loud and clear, sir.
很好,另外要f的是
All right. One more thing.
你今晚的任蘸荜PI
Your assignment tonight is strategic.
不能o橙艘源息之C
You can't give the enemy a break.
送他去地z
Send them to hell.
就@些
That is all.
敦V播,@是第八次新蟮
This is London calling. This is our eighth news bulletin.
(高利S尼K村L 阿方斯・利阿克斯)
@是一些c人有P的口信
Here are some personal messages.
「摩拉瑟斯明天О滋m地前怼
"Molasses tomorrow will bring forth cognac. "
「s翰L著LE子」
"John has a long mustache. "
重}
I repeat:
「s翰L著LE子」
"John has a long mustache. "
"John has a long mustache! "
「s翰L著LE子」
"John has a long mustache!"
不,不行……
No, not yet....
哦,我的天
Oh, my Lord!
「s翰L著LE子」
"John has a long mustache."
@表示什N,老兄？
Make any sense to you, mac?
我昨晚f^,是o法抵抗M的暗
As I said last night,they're code messages to the Resistance chaps.
@然,信息@M是@意思……
Obviously,one message means something to one group...
……ζ渌Mt是其他意思
...and another means something to another group.
「旅行社l生一起火摹
"There is a fire at the travel agency. "
重}
I repeat:
「旅行社l生一起火摹
"There is a fire at the travel agency. "
「用握
"Wounds my heart with a monotonous languor. "
重}
I repeat:
「用握
"Wounds my heart with a monotonous languor. "
四十五分後攻
The bridge, in 45 minutes.
我回淼
We' ll be back.
「用握
"Wounds my heart with a monotonous languor. "
重}
I repeat:
「用握
"Wounds my heart with a monotonous languor. "
「旅行社l生一起火摹
"There is a fire at the travel agency. "
(德第十五集F司令 　h斯・T・_穆特上)
整晚最好的一手牌
The best hand I've had all night.
我看看…….
Let me see here....
Σ黄
Pardon me.
Σ黄,④,砹
Pardon me, general, it's come.
等等,o我
Wait. Give that to me.
什N砹耍
What's come?
信息的第二部分
It's the second part of the message.
－魏的－是的,第二
-Verlaine.-Yes. The second verse.
「用握
"Wounds my heart with a monotonous languor."
可以A入侵⒃诙十四小r劝l
We can expect the invasion within 24 hours!
命令第十五集F全面戒
Put the 15th Army on full alert.
xx
Thank you.
@些我早已司空T,]什N可d^的
You know, I'm too old a bunny to get very excited about all this.
我出什N？哦,黑桃二
Now, where was I? Oh, yes, two spades!
真是y以置信
It's almost impossible to believe.
每c代表一艘船
Every dot represents a ship.
有鹋,巡洋,逐,呃淄
You got battlewagons, cruisers, destroyers, minesweepers.
有所有格型的攻粜痛b
You got assault craft of every size and every type.
@是有史以碜畲蟮呐
The biggest armada the world's ever known.
o
Here.
你住的
You remember it.
住每
Remember every bit of it.
@一天的前夜……
We're on the eve of a day...
……我死後人仍⒄很Lrg
...that people will talk about long after we're dead and gone.
想知道一件事幔
You wanna know something?
问⑴c其中就令我坐立不安
It gives me goose pimples just to be part of it.
你可以把它看成……
You could call it one of them...
……狂,}促的r婚姻之一
...crazy, quickie wartime marriages, you know?
是在谲舞上JR的……
Met at a dance at the USO and all that...
……不^我是J真的
...but, I mean, I took it serious.
她也是,我不问榱苏掖碳
And so did she. We didn't do it just for kicks.
－你什Nr候收到的信？－字芮
-When did you get the letter?-Week ago.
芍
Two weeks.
也S我不在信中那
Maybe I was wrong, what I wrote her.
我是f,她是高模特,而我……
I mean, she's a high-class model and all, and l....
我不是那NSS便便就Y婚的人
I'm not the kind of guy to get married that easy.
不拿@N事
I mean, it wasn't no joke to me.
不^夥,我真的有^一段美好r光
But oh, man, we really had some wonderful times together.
你X得她找了男朋友？
And you think she's got a boyfriend?
她]真正f起^…….
Well, she never actually said so....
我是f…….
I mean....
我@幔课沂钦f,公平幔
You think I was right? I mean, was I fair?
]你的允S她不能找e人不是幔
She can't get one without your permission, right?
必要你同意
You gotta give your okay.
我知道@是法律
I know it's the law.
它是檐婚而制的
They passed it for all the Dear Johns.
我想我最好是R上w
Well, I guess I better be getting back to the outfit.
祝你好\
Good luck.
你也是
You too.
那砘锸钦l？你和他聊了@N久？
Who was that guy? The one you was talking to so long?
我不JR,「麻雀」
I don't know, Sparrow.
我以前]^他
I never saw him before in my life.
你的ST祝你生日快,④
Happy birthday, general, from your staff!
xx
Thank you.
淝械案,L官？
Will you cut the cake, sir?
我相信你不希望我吃太多
I trust you don't expect me to eat it too!
(一九四四年六月六日)
(}洛,Z曼底)
那表示什N？
What's that?
笨蛋,那是表示倮的信,三短一L
Dummkopf, that's the "V for victory" sign.Three dots and a dash.
]^多芬的「第五交曲」幔
Ain't you never heard Beethoven's Fifth Symphony?
(Z曼底)
(英滑翔C突絷)
(由牛津和白金hpb步兵F和皇家工兵部的志者M成)
(W恩河,零c十一分)
到著c了,霍A德少校
Release point coming up, Major Howard.
好的,渲
Right, prepare for landing.
R上x
Cutting loose now.
收到,完
Roger and out.
(s翰・霍A德少校)
(英第六空降)
霍A德少校……
Major Howard...
……我不想高估你的任盏闹匾性
...I cannot overestimate the importance of your task.
但W恩河虮仨在橙四У糁前拿下
The Orne River Bridge must be captured...
...before the enemy can destroy it.
@是至P重要的事要道,橙艘炎骱谜ǖ羲的
It's a vital military artery,and the enemy has prepared it for demolition.
必出其不意K且完好地拿下
It must be taken by surprise and captured intact.
你⒃谌狈Φ孛嬷С值l件下於夜g著
Your gliders will land at night, without the benefit of ground support.
你要攻取颉…
You will assault the garrison, overwhelm it...
……K允刂敝猎到
...and hold until relieved.
允刂敝猎到
Hold until relieved.
霍A德少校
Major Howard!
看到蛄
There's the bridge coming up.
就在我左
Just on our left.
好了,大家手挽手
Right, link your arms.
打起精神
Brace yourselves.
抬_!
Feet up!
手挽o!
Hang on!
F,F
Smoke screen. Smoke.
n上去!n上去!
Up the action, bucks! Up the action, bucks!
好了,姆,上
Right, Tom. Over the bridge.
拆除爆破b置!
Check for demolition charges!
喂!喂!
Hello! Hello!
喂!死的!喂!
Hello! Damn it! Hello!
喂!喂!
Hello! Hello!
好了
Clear.
成功了!
It's working!
喂!喂!
Hello! Hello!
－t生在哪？－第三架滑翔C上
-Where's the doc?-On the third glider.
]收到他的蟾
There's no report from them.
－沃什－^？
-Walsh.-Sir?
姆他已得手了,你去接管
Tom, Ruskin and Royal have had it. Take over.
在虻牧硪活^
On the other end of the bridge.
－你怎N了？－著r弄嗔
-What happened to you?-Broke it on landing.
－t生]和你在一起？－他失了
-Isn't the doc with you?-No, he's missing.
我落在了河Y,只怕亡K重
We crashed in the river. Afraid we've got a lot of casualties.
我]事,^,弟兄一
I'm all right, sir. So are the boys.
－好,^m行樱好的,^,跟我!
-Okay, carry on.-Right, sir. Come on!
我真要…….
Well, I'll be....
嘿,t生,t生
Hey, doc! Doc!
你在那致铮磕沁是德人
What are you doing there? That's the German side.
L官,l都可能犯e
Sir, anybody can make a mistake.
^？
Sir?
爆破b置已拆除,氐装踩了
The demolition charges have been removed. It's all clear.
很好,史密斯下士
Good. Corporal Smith.
l送成功信,直到收到_J信
Send out the success code words.Keep sending until acknowledged.
－s翰,在碉堡O立指]部－好的,^
-John, set up HQ in that pillbox.-Right, sir.
不到十五分就搞定了
All in less than 15 minutes.
他的反攻只是rg}
Only a matter of time before they counterattack.
－惚呢？－第七惚I恐怕要敌r後才到
-What about the paratroopers?-7th Para might not get here for hours.
拉瓦特和他的突絷…….
And Lovat and his commandos....
可能要午後才能到
It could be midday before they get here.
}就是我能守多久了
The question is, how long can we hold?
守至援到
Hold until relieved.
(德第七集F⒅\L 克斯・彭塞少)
(德第七集F指]部)
天庹嬖,又下雨了
What awful weather. It's raining again.
xx
Thank you.
拿到名瘟幔
Did you get the list?
七○九L卡・T・施R本中⒁亚巴⒓鹌逋蒲
General Schlieben of the 709th has already left for the war games.
二四三L海因茨・赫密奇中⒁察锻砩狭c去了雷恩
The commander of the 243rd left for Rennes at 1800 hours.
有呢？
Who else?
有三五二的R默曼,共十二名官
Also, Zimmermann of the 352nd, 12 officers in all.
是啊,我知道
Yes, I know.
天獠缓,所以全都想在雷恩多享受一晚
The weather is bad,so everyone enjoys an extra night in Rennes.
我不喜g@
I don't like it.
一c都不
Any of it.
@N多重要官同r不在
So many key officers are away at the same time.
不知道槭颤N,但我就是不喜g
I don't know why, but I don't like it.
但鹌逋蒲菀恢芮熬投ê昧巳掌凇…
But the war games have been scheduled for a week....
,是明天,不是今晚
Yes, for tomorrow, not tonight.
建h所有尚未前往雷恩的官……
Advise all officers who have not yet left for Rennes...
……推t行程，到明天再f
...to postpone their departure until tomorrow.
容我提醒您,④……
May I remind you, general...
盟向硎窃诶硐氲奶l件下才登
that the Allies have always landed in perfect weather conditions.
北非,西西里,意大利…….
North Africa, Sicily, ltaly....
,是在黎明r分
Yes, and always at dawn.
我有十一分就要跳
We're 11 minutes from the green light.
F在,我再重}一次
Now, once more, I repeat:
如果意外降落到e`的地c……
If, for any reason, we fail to hit our drop zones...
……就朝|北方向前M
...move north by east.
|北方向
North by east.
德已淹]了海岸後方的大面e沼傻
The Germans have flooded large swamp areas behind the coast.
M量避_那
Avoid them if possible.
我是泶蛘,不是碛斡
We came here to fight, not to swim.
清楚]有？
Do you read me?
清楚了,L官
Loud and clear, sir.
Y果如何？
How'd you make out?
你加入局的Y果如何？
How did you make out at the game?
了
I lost.
F在我都能安全著了
Now we're both jumping clean.
我明白,元㈧逗r返回？
I understand. And when will the field marshal return?
知道了
I see. Oh, well.
等一下
Just a moment.
雷_蟾
The radar report.
我收到蟾嬲f雷_受到烈干_……
We are getting reports of strong radar interference...
……o接收也有阻K
...and radio reception is jammed.
我知道以前也有^,但奈慈绱乐
I realize this has happened before,but never this effectively!
而且……
And the--
打o西y部？好吧
Call the OB West? Very well.
元返回後代我候他
Give my respects to the field marshal when he returns.
(卡昂,凌晨一r○七分)
再,珀特,樯系,王,和你的家效力吧
Bye, Rupert. Do your duty for God, king, and your country.
求增援!我遭到攻!
Call for reinforcements! We're under attack!
往前走!上火!快!
Forward! Board! Fast!
－我硗砹幔
－不,不^……
-Are we late?
-No, but...
……我得s快!
...we must hurry!
怎N了？
What is it?
我去
I'll go.
站住!
Stop!
我f站住!
We said, stop!
站住,不然_了!
Stop, or I'll shoot!
你在@质颤N？
What are you doing here?
我住在那村子Y
I live in that farm.
那村子]人住
Nobody lives in that farm.
－是空的－出示你的C件
-It's abandoned.-Show me your papers.
快c!
Hurry up!
跟我走
Come with me.
快c!
Go on!
把_踏放在那
Put your bicycle there.
h斯!
Hans!
h斯,你在哪？
Hans, where are you?
－是怎N回事？－]什N事!
-What's going on here?-Nothing!
有l和你一起？快f!
Who is with you? I want to know!
停下!
Stop!
停下!停下!
Stop! Stop!
祝你在鹌逋蒲葜腥,④
Good luck at the war games, general.
有重要消息幔
Anything important?
通信兵蟾嬲f很y和前方取得M
Communications reports difficulty in contacting our forward posts.
又是地下M!
The Underground again!
有一些用降落憧战档南鹉z假人
Some sort of rubber dummies have been dropped by parachute.
橡z假人!
Rubber dummies!
o我接Y克特④
Connect me with General Richter!
我早料到有突u
和其他恐菩孕印…
We can expect commando raids and other diversionary tactics...
……但我不喜g假人惚@N主意
...but I don't like this idea of dummy parachutists.
我是R克斯,
Marcks speaking. Yes.
你肯定？
Are you certain?
有多少？
How many?
你有什N看法？
What do you think of it?
xx,Y克特
Thank you, Richter.
蟾嬲flF惚,@,@,有@
Paratroopers reported here, here and here!
放在那
Put it over there.
@就是空降的假人,碰到地面就爆炸
This is what they dropped,they explode on contact with the earth.
在黑暗中看起砭拖袷勘
In the dark, they look like soldiers.
也SY克特④看到的就是@,而不是真的惚
Perhaps these are what General Richter saw,not real paratroopers.
你M一次佯攻r,有某N目的
When you create a diversion, it's for a reason.
替我接彭塞④!
Connect me with General Pemsel!
假人……？!
Dummies...?!
橡z假人!
Rubber dummies!
我同意你的看法,④,我再打o你
I agree with you, general.I'll call you back.
接通T・德施泰特]有？
What about my call to von Rundstedt?
o法取得j,主志似乎被切嗔
We haven't been able to reach him.The main lines seem to be cut.
正在L其他j方式
Colonel Helmdach is trying to re-route the call.
他投下假人……
They wouldn't drop dummies...
……肯定是想D移我的注意力
...unless it was to divert our attention from something else.
在@N天猓
In this weather?
什N天舛家!
In any kind of weather!
我必j西y部
I must get in touch with OB West.
他是橙说惚!
They're enemy paratroopers!
鬼,夥……
Blimey, mate...
……你吵醒所有可旱牡兵
...you'll wake up the whole blooming German Army!
夥!
Fellas!
我被熳×!
I'm hung up!
夥!
Fellas!
－你]事吧？
－]事
-Are you all right?
-Yeah.
你是哪淼模
Where have you come from?
非常抱歉,老^
Awfully sorry, old man.
我在@褐的只能算是e差
Simply landed here by accident.
是l？
What's that?
抱歉到你了,我在找我的}餐餐具
Sorry I startled you. I'm trying to find my communion set.
－你的什N？
－}餐餐具,我把它弄G了
-Your what?
-My communion set. I've lost it.
著神父,我]rg碚摇…
Now listen, padre. We've got no time to look for--
我肯定是在@弄G的
I'm sure that it was here that I lost it.
我在火力之中,神父,你不X得……？
We're under fire, padre. Don't you think we ought to--?
你走吧,我的孩子,走,我很快就能找到
You go on, my boy. Go on. I'm sure I shall only be a minute.
老天!真是]k法
Cor! Stuff a grouse.
我找到了!我找到了!
I've got it! I've got it!
太好了
Glory be.
F在,我的孩子,我去完成上帝的使命
Now, my son, let's go about God's work this night.
我是普拉斯P
Pluskat.
(W克中校)
(德第三五二海防)
喂,普拉斯P,能到幔
Hello, Pluskat! Do you hear me?
我什N都]到…….
Nothing that I've heard....
是常有的爆炸,但相h
The usual bombing, but quite distant.
是的,我到了
Oh, yes, I can hear it.
等一下
Well, wait a minute.
是的,稍等一下
Yes, just a moment.
有W光,但x海岸很h
Flares, but a long way up the coast.
是的,瑟堡又遭到了攻
Yes, Cherbourg is getting hit again.
也S]什N事……
There's probably nothing to it...
……但是收到蟾嬲f有惚降落
...but we have had reports of paratrooper landings.
我去工事上看看
I'll go to my bunker and take a look.
xx,L官
Thank you, sir.
(}米伊格Y斯,凌晨二r○三分)
高一c!高一c!
Higher! Higher!
路易斯,打_你的店T,我要些桶子
Louis, open your store. We need more buckets!
雷ZL,你得R上跟我
Mayor Renaud, you must come with me immediately.
－有要o事幔浚非常要o,雷ZL
-Is it important?-Very important, Mayor Renaud.
怎N了,夫人？
What's wrong, madam?
我在去外小屋的路上…….
I was on my way to the little house outside....
好的,^mf
Yes, yes, go on.
突然看到有人奶於降
Suddenly, I saw a man fall from the sky.
－惚？－是的,一c]e
-A parachutist?-Yes, that's right.
看起砭拖裰话咨大B
He looked like a big white bird!
－英人是德人？－什N？
-British or German?-What?
那惚是朋友是橙耍
The parachutist, was he a friend or an enemy?
我不知道,他只f「u」,然後就不了
I don't know. He disappeared without a word. Just "Shh!"
－什N都]f－只f「u」
-Without a word?-Just "Shh!"
(法Z)早,女士
Bonjour, madame...
(法Z)我是美人
...je suis americain.
(法Z)早,小姐
Bonjour, mademoiselle...
(法Z)我是美人
...je suis americain.
我似乎在兜圈子
We seem to be circling.
]仕找不到降落地c了
Maybe they're having difficulty finding the drop zone.
Je suis...
...amercan.
Je suis amricain.
Voulez-vous...
...mademoiselle?
好了
Okay.
跳!
Go!
跳!跳!跳!
Go! Go! Go!
惚!
Paratroopers!
惚部!惚部!
Paratroop groups.Those are paratroop groups!
有]有新消息？
Anything new?
瑟堡那和平r一颖炸不唷…
Heavy bombing over Cherbourg as usual, sir...
……F在接近卡昂了
...and now near Caen.
第六和第八炮位的路被切唷…
The lines to Stations 6 and 8 have been cut...
……但指]路能接通
...but the direct line is open.
我在@呆
I'll stay for a while.
－要咖啡幔浚好的,xx
-Would you like coffee?-Yes, thank you.
看在上帝份上,神父,e再弄出音
For God's sakes, padre, stop that damn noise.
抱歉,孩子,我恐怕迷路了
I'm sorry, son. I'm afraid I'm lost.
有l不怕？跟我
Well, who ain't? Now, come on.
陕「卡嗒」
Two clicks.
我到是陕「卡嗒」
I heard two clicks.
老兄……
Man...
……很高d到你
...am I glad to see you.
－你是八十二空降幔浚不,是一○一空降
-You guys the 82nd?-No. This is the 101.
一○一？
101?
那八十二空降呢？
Where's the 82nd?
夥,我也不知道自己的大部在哪
Look, bud, we don't even know where our own outfit is.
有人在攻Ψ
Well, somebody's shooting at somebody.
我去看看r
Let's us go find this war.
戆
Come on.
也S是英佬,他]有「蟋蟀」
Maybe they're Limeys and ain't got no cricket.
肯定是自己人
They must be our guys.
好吧
Okay.
不
No.
嘿
Hey.
嘿,他是德人
Hey, they were Germans.
有蛋偌茱wC奈膳燥w^
Hundreds of planes have been flying to my left and right.
是朝卡昂方向
Toward Caen.
是的
Yes.
F在w^瑟堡半u了,一定有情r!
Now over the Cherbourg peninsula. Something must be happening!
什N情r,普拉斯P,什N情r？ 我一c都不明白
But what, Pluskat, what? I haven't the faintest idea.
海┥习lF什N情r]有？
Has anything been observed on the beaches?
不,什N都]有
No, nothing.
好的,我Sr向你蟾
Yes, I'll let you know right away.
然
Of course.
你肯定是踝骨嗔耍
Are you positive that ankle's broken?
秃瞎钦,^
Compound fracture, sir.
把靴子穿回去,M好靴,Mo!
Well, put the boot back on and lace it up, tight.
el火,又不是我弄嗟
Don't get mad, I didn't break it.
你也不必用它走路
And you're not walking on it.
－你不是想……－e再f了,照我f的做
-You're not going to try---Knock it off and do as you're told.
什N事？
Yes?
Ａ,Ｂ,ＣB和我一尤走散了
A, B and C Company are scattered all over like we are.
有呢
Go on.
康克林少校落在石上摔嗔思绨,我把他留ol生T了
Major Conklin landed on a stone wall, broke his shoulder.I left him with a medic.
j到ＦB]有？
Any contact with F Company?
]有,但他肯定在前面,}米伊格Y斯方向
No, but they must be up ahead in the direction of Sainte-Mere-Eglise.
e停下,M好,M好
Well, go ahead. Tie it off. Tie it off.
@是我的位置
Well, here's where we are.
在沼傻氐谋倍恕…
The northern edge of the swamp area...
……xA定著c有五英里
...five miles from our drop zone.
五英里
Five miles.
－是ＦB幔
－不,L官
-F Company?
-No, sir.
我四搜索^了
And we've got scouts all over the place.
找到了一○一空降的一弟兄
We even picked up a group from the 101.
ＦB是在I航的第一架wC上
F Company were the first of the lead planes.
扶我一把
Well, give me a hand.
把我的o我
Can I have my rifle?
我朝@方向走
Well, we'll head out this way.
天亮r我能到_高地或者_地
We ought to reach high ground  and open country by daybreak.
好了,大家分散_怼…
All right. Have the men spread out...
……沿途召集走散的弟兄
...pick up any stragglers they can find.
－把飨氯
－是,L官
-Pass the word.
-Right, sir.
大家分散_,聚n掉的弟兄
All right, men, spread out. Pick up stragglers you see.
把飨氯
Pass the word down.
好了……
All right...
……我出l
...Iet's go.
根最新的蟾,我的看法是……
From the latest reports, this is how I see it:
美惚已降落在…….
American paratroopers have landed....
……@
...here.
英惚在@
British paratroopers here.
M攻…….
The invasion....
……@
...here.
是的,xx,彭塞
Yes. Thank you, Pemsel.
彭塞④_信@是入侵
General Pemsel is convinced that this is the invasion.
我不同意,我的看法是……
I do not agree with him. This is my conclusion:
Z曼底只是恐菩怨舻哪
Normandy is the objective of a diversionary attack.
是恐菩怨,布T特Y特
A diversionary attack, Blumentritt.
不是主要攻裟,主目耸羌尤R……
It's not the main attack.That will come at the Pas-de-Calais...
……早就A料到的地c
...where it was always expected.
那是我A料的地c
Where we always expected it.
但我不能掉以p心
But we can't take any chances.
立刻出友b甲A潢
I want the reserve panzers moved up at once!
必^元首y部的同意
We need approval from the Fuhrer's headquarters.
他不敢拒^我的要求
They wouldn't dare refuse me!
打o元首y部
Call the Fuhrer's headquarters and insist.
Insist that the panzers be released to me immediately!
M攻Z曼底悖x了事常
An invasion of Normandy would be against all military logic.
在是悖x所有常
It would really be against all logic.
大概就是@些了,各位
Well, that about covers it, gentlemen.
你大部分以前有^登
Most of you have had your feet wet before:
敦克克,迪耶普,挪威
Dunkirk, Dieppe, Norway.
大家都知道被s下海是指什N
And we know what it means to be driven into the sea.
仔r後我要暮Ｉ⒒厝
In a few hours we're going back from the sea.
@次我要站住_
And this time we're going to stay.
]有rg橛⒏裉m,家@,以及美女而感
There's no time for any sob stuff about...
...England, home and beauty.
住,我的同胞已受苦受y四年半了
Remember, our people have had a rough time for four and a half years.
他A得最後的倮
They've earned the final victory.
我F它
Let's give it to them.
於中的法鹩,我要f……
And to our French comrades in arms, I say:
祝你好\
Good luck.
明早,我要打∷
Tomorrow morning, we'll take them.
M,泰迪,　　 就@影,中士
-
Come in, Teddy. That will be all, sergeant.
M,泰迪,　　 就@影,中士
(美第四步兵副L 西W多・_斯福准)
你一定要M蟾幔
Did you have to put it in writing?
不@幽憔筒我去
I knew you wouldn't let me go unless I did.
你@是o我出y}
You're putting me on the spot.
－我不是有意的,塔比－不是才怪
-I didn't mean to, Tubby.-The hell you didn't.
你都⒄求M了正式蟾
You put that request in writing, made it official.
你可是副L
You're the assistant division commander.
所以我第一波上岸
And that's why I'm supposed to go ashore in the first wave.
我去那,你知道的
That's where I'm supposed to be.  You know that.
你@次行雍苤匾
You're important to this operation.
我不能在第一天就失去你
We can't have you knocked off on the first day.
可那不是真正的理由
But that's not the real reason.
是不是因槲腋赣H是美y？
Isn't it because my father was president of the United States?
而且是了不起的y
And a great president.
也是了不起的人
And a great soldier.
他曾ьI「FT兵」攻下了}胡安山
He led the charge of the Rough Riders up San Juan Hill.
所以F在你想成榈谝登上「q他海」的人
So now you've got to be the first man ashore on Utah Beach.
可那是我去的地方,@是我的
But that's where I'm supposed to be, Tubby. That's my job.
而且我和部下一起v^所有
Also, I've been there side by side with the men all through training.
他T看到我在,也有嗬期待我在
They're used to seeing me there.They have a right to expect me there.
不管是不是y的鹤
President's son or not.
我的求被拒^了？
Is my request denied?
不,你知道不的
No, you know it's not.
被很不情地批准了
Request reluctantly approved.
xx,塔比
Thanks, Tubby.
非常感x
Thanks a lot.
那N……
Say...
……你的P炎怎N恿耍
...how's that arthritis of yours?
P炎？
Arthritis?
好月]l作了
Haven't had a touch in months.
真是好消息
Glad to hear it.
街道……
The street...
……颉…
...the bridge...
……旅^……
...the hotel...
……
...the casino.
(法突絷指]官 菲力普・基佛海中校)
就是@,各位
That's it, gentlemen.
另外……
One more thing....
四年砟D鸶鞣健…
You have been fighting everywhere for four years...
……阿比西尼,利比,埃及,克里特u……
...in Abyssinia, Libya, Egypt, Crete....
但@次你是在法的I土上作稹…
But this time you are going to fight on French soil...
……是在我的土地……
...in our fields...
……我的l村……
...in our villages...
……我同胞的眼皮底下
...under the eyes of our own people.
我可不能檫@自相矛盾的蟾娼行言首
(阿弗雷德・s德上)
(德武b部最高y部作鸩坎块L)
I can't wake the Fuhrer on the strength of contradictory reports.
(阿弗雷德・s德上)
(德武b部最高y部作鸩坎块L)
他吃^o┰谒X,要四c起床
He was up till four. He took a sedative and then retired.
我不能檫@些蟾娉承阉
I won't wake him for these reports.
最初的蟾嬲f惚是被袈滹wC上的CM人T
First we hear that the paratroopers are shot down plane crews.
然後又被f成是橡z假人
Next they are identified as mechanical dummies.
即使蟾娑际钦娴亩且惚已著……
If these reports are true and paratroopers have landed...
……也可能只是一次突u而已
...it can only be a commando raid.
@N理由足以派b甲部前往海岸幔
Is that a sufficient reason to send the panzers to the coast?
元首醒後我M快⑦@些蟾嫣峤唤o他
I will submit all reports to the Fuhrer as soon as he awakens.
明白了
I understand.
s德拒^了求
Jodl has turned us down.
]有元首的批准，他不⒀b甲部交o我……
He will not release the panzers without the Fuhrer's approval...
……而元首在睡X!
...and the Fuhrer is still asleep!
要通知T・德施泰特幔
Will you tell von Rundstedt?
不,r不用…….
No, not now....
r不用
Not now.
xx,各位
Thank you, gentlemen.
坐吧
Sit down.
@是v史性的
This is history.
我正在一v史性的r刻，我要掉@了……
We are living a historical moment.
We are going to lose the war...
……就因ゴ蟮脑首吃了一w安眠……
...because the glorious Fuhrer has taken a sleeping pill...
……所以不能被吵醒
...and is not to be awakened.
真是y以置信
It's unbelievable.
想想@一刻,特
Think of it, Kurt.
永he忘了@一刻
Don't ever forget it.
我正在C一件事……
We are witnessing something...
……v史W家一直f@^o可能……
...which historians will always say is completely improbable...
……但s千真f_
...and yet it is true.
元首不能被吵醒!
The Fuhrer is not to be awakened!
有r我真想知道上帝是站在哪一
I sometimes wonder whose side God is on.
要我……
Can l...
……槟拿c什N幔
...bring you anything, sir?
我房gY有一瓶上等的干邑白m地……
In my room there is a bottle of excellent cognac...
……「拿破觥,]_^
...Napoleon, unopened.
我本想留到一合m的龊显匍_
I was even saving it for a fitting occasion.
F在算不上合m的龊,可是拿碓僬f吧
This isn't exactly the right occasion, but get it anyway.
算天亮了
Daylight at last.
又浪M了一整夜!
A whole night wasted again!
我的狗呢？
Where's my dog?
才在@呢
He was here a minute ago.
最後再看一下
Let's have one last look.
什N都]有
Nothing.
B只海t都]……
Not even a seagull....
我的天!
My God!
入侵
The invasion.
他砹!
They're coming!
各就各位!
Everyone to your posts!
是入侵!海上至少有五千艘船!
It's the invasion!  There must be 5000 ships out there!
o一c,普拉斯P
Get hold of yourself, Pluskat.
耻的船bB那一半都不到
The enemy doesn't have even half that many.
死的,自己^砜纯窗,你@白V!
Well, damn it!  Come and see for yourself, you fool!
太@人了
It's amazing.
真不敢相信
It's beyond belief.
H鄣钠绽斯P,那些船在朝哪_？
My dear Pluskat, where are these ships heading?
n我@砹!
Straight for me!
(美第一集F司令 　WR・牙椎吕中)
④,煞昼之後……
General, in exactly two minutes...
……就㈤_火
...the fleet will open fire.
注意,④l表v
Your attention, please.The admiral has an announcement.
(「自由法」武b力量　朱雅德海少)
我很快⒐s地投身於痿Y之中
Soon we will have the honor to be engaged in battle.
榱粟s走橙,我不得不向自己的I土_火
To drive the enemy out, we must fire on our homeland.
@是自由的代r
This is the price of liberty.
法m西fq!
Long live France!
他去了,很r,和往常一
There he goes, right on time, as usual.
他要上岸了!他砹!他砹!
They're landing! They're coming! They're coming!
我],看,他快上岸了!
I'm not crazy. Look, they're landing!
美人,英人,有法人!
The Americans, the English and the French!
普拉斯P,到]有？你怎N回事？到底怎N回事？
Do you hear me? What's the matter with you? What's going on?
你一定是@了!y道……？
You must be deaf! Can't you...?
死的,y道你]幔
Damn it, can't you hear it for yourself?
我正遭到攻! 是的,遭到攻!
We're under fire. Yes, under fire!
你f盟弄不到的那五千艘船……
Those 5000 ships you say the Allies haven't got...
……他弄到了!
...well, they've got them!
真是太好了!
It's wonderful!
喂？又有什N事？
Yes? What is it now?
我f,「匹普斯」
Listen to me, Pips.
入侵已_始!R上M入戒B!
The invasion has started!  Put yourself on alert at once!
就
What the hell can I do with only two planes?
其他wC在哪？你@白V!
Where are the others, you idiots?!
普Y勒,@是命令!R上!明白了幔
Priller, that's an order!  Get ready at once! Understand?
如果不是太麻┑脑……
If it isn't too much trouble...
……能告V我入侵地c是在哪幔
...would you tell me where the invasion is?
什N？Z曼底!真是太妙了!
What? Normandy! How delightful!
x了,我忠的h斯,@下我完了!永e了!
Thanks, my faithful Hans. That's the end for us! So long!
在@想睡好X真是太y了
It's getting very difficult  to get any sleep around here.
你浜瞄L眠不醒吧,入侵已_始了
Your prospects for a long sleep are excellent.The invasion has begun.
Z曼底,我要w往那,我z
Normandy. We're flying there, the two of us.
]有其他人
Nobody else is left.
我恐怕是回不砹
I don't think we're coming back.
「WR哈海」
(凌晨六r三十二分)
_始行!_始行!
Move out! Move out!
Z炸已停止
The shelling has stopped.
登艇正在接近
Landing craft approaching.
回到你的指]部,到那Y指]你的部!
Return to headquarters. Direct your troops from there!
登艇正在接近海岸!
Landing craft approaching the coast!
那些法混蛋!
Those French bastards!
中士!
Sergeant!
派人把@送到部去
Send this to headquarters by courier.
不!你H自去,告V他路被切嗔
No! Take it yourself. Tell them our lines are cut!
各位,^
Gentlemen, come here please.
涔!
Attack!
快!
Fast!
各就各位!
Take your positions!
e他靠得太近!
Don't let them get too close!
快!
Fast!
涔!
Attack!
就是那,弟兄,「WR哈海」,死神就在前
There it is, men.  Omaha Beach, dead ahead.
瞄誓!
Lock on the target!
湫!
Stand by!
快x_海!
Get off of the beach!
我走!
Let's go!
快,前M!
Come on, move up!
你好,④先生
Hello, general, sir.
－你]事吧,小子？－]事,L官
-Are you all right, boy?-Yes, sir.
你不X得回去拿上你的比^好幔
Don't you think you better go back and get your rifle?
去那,L官？
Out there, sir?
今天Y束以前你肯定用得著它
You're almost sure to need it before this day is over.
是,L官
Yes, sir.
快!前M!前M
Come on! Move on up! Let's go.
t生!t生!
Medic! Medic!
④,「WR哈海」淼牡谝环蟾
General, first reports from Omaha, sir.
「突舨筷已登
"Assault teams have landed.
「尚未取得台j,但是逐蟾嬲f……
No direct radio contact, but destroyers report...
「……第一和第二波似乎被困在海┥
...first and second waves appear pinned down on the beach.
「遭到炮兵和迫襞诩中攻
Concentrated artillery and mortar fire.
「第三波前M困y」   亡K重,L官
Third wave floundering."Heavy casualties, sir.
(「q他海」)
(凌晨六r四十四分)
等迫襞诤C安o下碇後……
When the mortars and machine guns are silenced...
……要各挝恢]官在那和我碰^
...have the battalion commanders join me over there.
明白
Okay.
把地D拿好,艾迪
Hang on to that map case, Eddie.
我成功了
I made it.
嘿,我成功了
Hey, I made it.
看到我撂倒那砘]有？
Did you see me get those two guys?
嘿,中士？
Hey, sergeant?
中士？
Sergeant?
我估,@不是正_的地c
As best as I can figure it, this is the wrong beach.
我是在A登c以南一又四份之一英里
We're a mile and a quarter south of where we were supposed to land.
我在那上岸
We should be up there.
指]船一定是被海面的炮火F弄糊T了
Control boat must've been confused by the naval bombardment smoke.
我同意,那F在怎Nk？
I agree with you, but what will we do now?
援和重型武器追昼染到
Reinforcements and heavy equipment will approach in a very few minutes.
－我知道,我知道－如果他是在正_地c登呢？
-I know, I know.-What if they land at the right beach?
不管我在哪,援兵都得跟著我
The reinforcements will have to follow us wherever we are.
我就倪@洪_始M攻
We're starting the war from right here.
－我向汝前M－好的,出l
-Head inland. We're going inland.-Okay, let's go.
跟o我,照我的幼幼!
Follow me. Do everything I do!
好了,出l!
All right. Let's go!
「金海」,「朱Z海」
(凌晨六r四十分)
回家了!
Head for home!
@是德空v史上最美好的一刻!
The Luftwaffe has had its great moment!
(「海」)
(凌晨六r五十三分)
Stand by to beach.
肯,小心那c
Duncan, take care of that strongpoint.
Sr湫!
Any minute now. Stand by!
我槎乜克以色!
Let's give it them back for Dunkirk!
敦克克,你到]有,克拉夫？
You hear that? Dunkirk. Do you hear it, Clough?
那核乳臭未乾呢
Sure he was at school at the time.
戆,你@些U物!
Come on, you bums!
出,你@些下流坯! 弗拉
Come out, you dirty slobs! Flanagan's back!
]打仗就o淹死,那可太不幸了
The evil of it all. Drowning a man before he fights.
哦,戆!
Oh, come on!
v^m前M!
Keep those vehicles moving!
兵,跟上那些T自行的
MP, chase out those cyclists.
(英皇家海海┲]官 科林・莫德海上校)
x_海!
Get off the beach!
向汝前M!
Move inland!
你快c!
Come on, you lot!
s快
Hurry it up.
e在@f聊!
Never mind the blathering!
我要把b涠及差D好
We must put these down somewhere.
你越早x_海……
The sooner you get off the beach...
……他就越早停止@可旱呐
...the sooner they'll stop this blasted shelling.
炮著我的狗!
It's very bad for the dog!
o,厮诡D,o!
Down, Winston, down!
「海」海┲]官,２－Ａ^
Beach Master Sword, Section 2-A.
第三波已r登,後m行游词茏璧K
Third wave ashore on time. No obstruction to follow-up.
待命中
Standing by.
_始行!
Get going!
看在上帝的份上,把它弄出海!
For heaven's sake, get that carrier off the beach!
我f可以用你的ol
I was told I could transmit a newsflash on your radio.
如果不能_走,就把它搬走!
If you can't drive it, carry it!
你f什N？
You were saying?
有人f可以用你的o……
I was told I could transmit a newsflash on your--
H鄣拟酚,我不想@得不合作……
My dear fellow, I don't want to appear uncooperative--
不e,我知道媒w的力量
Yes, I know all about the power of the press.
但@l得忙更重要的事!快c!
But this line happens to be rather busy! Come on!
o,厮诡D,o,厮诡D
Down, Winston. Down, Winston.
他怎Nf？
What did he say?
他f不行
The answer is no.
只好用死的子了
We have to use the damn pigeons.
好在我早有
I've got these ready.
,上去吧
Here, clip this on.
它we了方向
They're going the wrong way.
那是德人,白V!
Not toward the Germans, you idiots!
是@!是@!
The other way! The other way!
死的叛徒!
Damned traitors!
－恐它－你就不能把你的手指拿出硎幔
-Hold it.-Can't you get your finger out?
－怎N回事？－引擎o法,L官
-What's the matter?-Engine won't start, sir.
我想是M了海水
Full of seawater, I think.
我的老祖母常f……
My old grandmother used to say...
……C械有什N}就狠狠揍它
...anything mechanical, give it a good bash.
F在
Try it now.
xx,L官
Thank you, sir.
走吧,祝你好\
Off you go. Good luck.
@一下可真有用
I'm sure that got it out.
@就是我f的害角色!
That's what I call a hell of a man!
我也喜g他的狗
Aye, I like his dog too.
e在那U了!
Don't stand there yapping!
@可不是海德公@!是!
This isn't Hyde Park Corner! The war's over there!
跟上!
Come along!
快!
Come on!
－xx－一切都很利
-Thank you.-Everything's going according to plan.
等待行用令,米林,「
Stand by to move. Millin, "Blue Bonnet."
搞什N鬼……？
What in God's name...?
我的朋友,多N美好的一天!
Oh, my friends. What a day! What a day!
g迎淼椒!g迎淼礁呃S尼K!
Welcome to France. Welcome to Colleville!
你太好了,真是幸……
Most kind of you. Very nice to meet you--
看,我一直留著@
Look at this. I kept it for you all.
不^恐怕不虼蠹液鹊
But I don't think there will be enough for everyone.
也S下次吧,我另有As:打仗!
Perhaps next time. We have a previous engagement: the war!
不必浪M香了!
Mustn't lose that champagne!
好了,大家集合! 米林,「
All right, men, fall in! Millin, "Blue Bonnet."
再
Goodbye.
xx,小伙子!xx!
Thank you, boys! Thank you!
法m西fq!盟fq!
Long live France! Long live the Allies!
要我f的……
If you ask me, Flanagan...
……@海┥险嬗胁簧俟殴值砘
...there's a lot of very peculiar blokes on this beach.
g迎!
Welcome!
g迎大家!
Welcome to you all!
xx,H鄣,@鞋真漂亮!
Thank you, dear, they're lovely!
最好先穿上
Better try them on first.
我是隆美
Rommel speaking.
早
Good morning.
什N？
What?
什N!
What!
哪？
Where?
Z曼底!
Normandy!
他已登了幔
Have they a foothold already?
必阻止他!
They must be thrown back!
b甲A潢呢？
What about the panzer reserves?
T・德施泰特脑首那@取指]]有？
Did von Rundstedt obtain their release from the Fuhrer?
Z曼底,Z曼底
Normandy, Normandy.
我真是愚蠢!
How stupid of me!
愚蠢
Stupid.
(霍克岬c　清晨七c十一分)
就是那
There it is.
你是f我得哪桥郎先幔
You mean to tell me that's all we gotta climb?
]有爬的那N高
They're not as high as the practice ones.
r可]有炮火
They wasn't shooting at us then.
槭颤N不空或是海郑
Why can't the Air Force or Navy do this job?
目罩锌床坏已箩崦嫜隗w鹊拇笈
The big guns in bunkers behind the cliff can't be seen from the air.
不值羲,它就值粑海┥系牡苄
We knock them out or they'll murder our guys on the beach.
是啊,要我f的……
Yeah, well, if you ask me...
……三老太婆用咧憔湍馨盐一吖
...three grandmothers with brooms could sweep us off there...
……就像奶痫上Z走n一
...like flies off of a sugar cake.
就是它,我要找的目
That's it, the one we're after.
是空的
It's empty.
空和海_o了他好看
The Air Force and Navy really plastered this baby.
可我]明白……
But I don't get--
@些炮
The guns.
都]有架好
There ain't no mounts.
根本就]有安b^
They've never even been installed.
你是f……
You mean...
我M了@N大的
we come up all this way
s只是一鐾冢
for nothing?
e心,你不有事
Don't worry, sarge, you'll be all right.
t生!t生!
Medic! Medic!
(德Z) 「e!」, 「e!」
"Bitte!", "Bitte!"
他\哩咕５脑谡f什N？
I wonder what "Bitte, Bitte" means.
你穿著救生衣搞什N鬼？
What the hell are you wearing a life preserver for?
我不游泳
I can't swim.
Z曼底,真的是Z曼底
Normandy. It really is Normandy.
真是狂,狂,粹是狂!
This is madness, madness, sheer madness!
什N事？
What is it?
我和s德④通^,元首已醒了
I just talked to General Jodl, the Fuhrer is awake.
我才不在乎他醒]醒!b甲A潢的事怎N樱
I don't care if he's awake or not!What about the reserve panzers?
元首在大l雷霆……
The Fuhrer went into one of his tantrums...
……所以]人敢提任何事
...and no one dared bring up the subject.
那就是於AB!
They're still held in reserve!
是的,元
Yes, field marshal.
L官,如果你H自打o元首……
Sir, if you would call the Fuhrer yourself...
……我相信他尊重你的看法
...I am convinced he would respect your views.
打o他？
Call him?
打o那波希米下士？!
Call that Bohemian corporal?!
要我向他奴卑膝？!
Crawl on my knees to him?!
不!B想都不要想!
No! It is out of the question!
「用握
"Wounds my heart with a monotonous languor."
什N意思？
What's that?
]什N,已]有意x了
Nothing, nothing of importance.
,我湍
Here, let me help you.
你好吧,姆？快,他在上
You all right, Tom?  Come on, they're up there.
－^－怎N？
-Sir.-Well?
史密斯要我D告你,他的人已浜
Mr. Smith says to tell you he's stood his men too.
德еC和迫襞谕七M到了淞盅Y
The Jerries are moving up into the woods...
...with machine guns and mortars.
－要弟兄做好!－告V弟兄……
-Tell the men to stand firm!-Tell the chaps--
付橙讼乱惠猛烈反攻
Tell them to expect another counterattack, a heavy one.
－拿著,夥－xx
-Here you are, mate.-Ta.
－什N事？－
-What's the matter?-Listen.
我到了L笛
I thought I heard bagpipes.
e傻了!
Don't be daft!
我告V你到了L笛!是援兵
I told you I heard bagpipes! It's the reinforcements.
是拉瓦特!
It's Lovat!
快!
Come on!
－抱歉硗砹耍比不硪好
-Sorry I'm late.-Better than never, sir.
真高d到你,希米
Glad to see you, Shimmy.
你正好被成了靶子,情r如何？
You boys are right on target. What's the situation?
德在一英里外的淞种兄匦虏渴
Jerry's regrouping in the woods, about a mile.
有迫襞诤椭C
With mortars and heavy machine guns.
有多少？
Numbers?
不知道,希米,但似乎正在集Y更多兵力
No idea, Shimmy, but they seem to be moving forward in force.
那拥脑,我就更不能等了
In that case, we won't wait.
最好是行
We'd better get moving.
好了,我要穿^去
All right, we're going across.
－米林!－是？
-Millin!-Sir?
吹「黑熊」
"Black Bear," sir.
好了,戆
All right, come on.
都起!
Everybody up!
出l!
On your feet!
是他,他又在吹了
There he goes. He's at it again.
你@子^@Ny的音幔
Ever hear such a bleeding racket in all your life?
]e,m人吹L笛就是@
Yeah, it takes an Irishman to play the pipes.
允刂猎兵到
Hold until relieved.
北偏|方向,北偏|方向,}米伊格Y斯在@
North by east, north by east. Sainte-Mere-Eglise is that way.
有人移舆^路
Somebody turned that sign around.
Y除了我就]人看一下指南幔
Doesn't anybody in this outfit look at a compass besides me?
嘿,夥
Hey, you guys!
^!^!
Over here! Over here!
^,跑步!
Over here, on the double.
－要把它弄到哪去？－不知道,L官
-Where you taking that?-We don't know, sir.
我走e了路
We took the wrong road.
Y面有什N？幔
What do you got in here, ammo?
是的,L官
Yes, sir.
－你是八十二空降？－不,L官,是一○一空降
-You 82nd?-No, sir, 101.
F在你w八十二空降了
Well, you're in the 82nd now.
－可是L官……－可是什N？
-But, sir, we're---But what?
]什N,L官
Nothing, sir.
好了,出l
All right, move out.
－把路税蔚!－是,L官
-Knock that sign down!Yes, sir.
－上面有|西移,中校－P倒!掩蔽
-Something's moving up there, colonel.-Hit the dirt! Take cover.
是ＡB的西恩中尉,^
Lieutenant Sheen, sir, A Company.
中校,是我!
Colonel, it's me!
－你哪恚浚}米伊格Y斯
-Where did you come from?-Sainte-Mere-Eglise.
我控制了主要道路和V霰
We hold the main road and north side of the square.
德有一炮兵B在子的另一……
The Germans have a battery on the other side of the town...
－……控制著l村地^－m斯少校呢？
-...and command the countryside.-And Major Lance?
－埋伏在V龅囊淮苯êBY－ＦB呢？
-Holed up in a building in the square.-F Company?
他w^了空降地c,降落到了中心
They overshot the drop zone and landed in the middle of the town.
^mf
Go on.
那是,一鐾
It was a nightmare, sir. A slaughter.
在著地之前就被全了
They were mowed down before they hit the ground.
m斯少校派我砗湍懵j
Major Lance sent me to try and contact you, sir.
他想要你批准撤退,然後在外重新部署
He wants your permission
to pull back and regroup outside of town.
不,死的,我要拿下}米伊格Y斯
No, damn it. We came here to take Sainte-Mere-Eglise.
要拿下K守住它
We're gonna take it and hold it.
跟著中尉,弟兄
Follow the lieutenant, gentlemen.
－L官
－xx
-Sir.
-Thank you.
英,加绍正"海","金海"和"朱Z海"步推M
British and Canadians advancing steadily from Sword, Gold, and Juno.
「WR哈海」有消息幔
Anything from Omaha?
只收到了第一l消息:激,亡K重
Nothing since the first message:heavy fighting, heavy casualties.
L官
Sir.
「WR哈海」淼模
Omaha?
不是
No.
真搞不懂德槭颤N不投入重型b甲部
I can't understand why Jerry hasn't brought his heavy armor into play.
除了二十一b甲,其Nb甲……
All the panzer divisions except the 21st...
……似乎都h在後方
...seem to be sitting it out in the rear.
L官
Sir.
「法突絷摹海』直汝……
"French commandos driving inland from Sword...
……已到_跻了固乩瞻航纪狻
...have reached the outskirts of Ouistreham."
跻了固乩瞻
Ouistreham.
撤退!
Fall back!
掩蔽!
Take cover!
坦克支援!我需要坦克支援!
Tank support! We must have tank support!
呼叫「巴士底」,呼叫「巴士底」,我是「厣」,回答,「巴士底」!
Hello, Bastille. Hello, Batille.This is Windsor. Come on, Bastille!
_火!
Fire!
注意!
Attention!
_火!
Fire!
呼叫「巴士底」,呼叫「巴士底」,我是「厣」,回答,「巴士底」!
Hello, Bastille. Hello, Batille.This is Windsor. Come on, Bastille!
o法取得j!
I can't get them!
^m!我必有支援!
Keep trying! We must have support!
允位,我去找v坦克!
Hold your positions. I'm going for a tank!
M可能o我掩o!
Give us as much cover as you can!
,右!
The bridge, right!
_火!
Fire!
值裟情T大炮!
Try for the cannon!
把T弄出去!
Get the wounded out of here!
回去!
Go back!
x_@!
Get out of here!
不!回去!
No! Go back!
你不能留在@!
You can't stay here!
我是修道院的院L
I am Mother Superior of the convent.
@些修女都是合格的o士
The Sisters are qualified nurses.
可是夫人…… 我是f,,我正在打仗!
But madame-- I mean, Mother, we're in the middle of a battle!
失陪,照T
Excuse me. Take care of the wounded.
是坦克!
It's a tank!
是基佛!
It's Kieffer!
在另一!
In the other direction!
清除碎石!快!
Clear away the debris! Hurry!
我的空在哪？!
But where is the Luftwaffe?!
－我正在M
－好的,好的,快找吧
-I'm trying.
-Yeah, yeah, you're trying.
英攻下了一╊^地,正向汝挺M
The British troops have a beachhead here.They are moving inland.
美最I了}米伊格Y斯,K切嗔斯路
The Americans hold Ste-Mere-Eglise and have cut the highway.
我控制著中央地
We control this center section.
美m已登,但他被我困住了
The Americans have landed but their attack has bogged down.
隆美f得
Rommel is right.
如果我能⑺困在海┥稀…
If we can hold them on the beaches...
……入侵就落空
...the invasion will collapse.
t生!
Medic!
@玩意能用幔
That thing still work?
是的,L官,偶能用
Yes, sir, now and then.
－有]有其他╊^的消息？－o法直接j
-Anything from the other beaches?-Not directly.
有人收到尿逐l出的W光信
A while ago the sergeant picked up some flashes from the destroyers.
第四已x_「q他海」向汝挺M
The 4th Division is off Utah Beach and moving inland.
汝？
Inland?
－第一呢？－他被困住了,L官
-What about the 1st Division?-They're hung up, sir.
和我一
Like we are.
行
Move out.
t生!
Medic!
－你有什N想法？－想法？
-What do you think?-Think?
我F在死至少有一千人
We must have close to 1000 casualties up to now.
要j船b斫游幔
Do you want me to have the ships start picking us up?
－你J橛羞@釉悖浚我看不出有其他x
-You think it's that bad?-I don't see what else to do.
我o法登上山^
We can't get up this hill.
如果不能x_海,我全覆]
If we don't get off this beach,we won't have any division left.
什N？
What?
@是我的部下,姆
These are our men, Tom.
他黼y道是榱怂退,然後剩下的人逃跑幔
You think we brought them in so some die and ask the rest to turn tail?
鬼,不,我要拿下那山^
Hell, no. We're gonna get up that hill.
派人去把「pT兵」(突絷)o我找
Find me somebody to speak for the Rangers.
海┍趁嬗扔幸l溪谷
Back down the beach on the right there's a gully.
有一支重兵把守,扔Cv守
With a heavily defended roadblock and machine gun nests on both sides.
－如果我能㈤_一l路……－^三次了
-If we can blow our way through---We've hit it three times.
－根本o法接近－三次不算多
-We didn't get close.-Three times isn't enough.
我要再,能找些工兵幔
We're gonna hit it again. Can you find me some engineers?
到都是!
They're all around you!
我是指в锌捎醚b涞墓け
I mean engineers with equipment still working.
不用和船bj幔
Then I shouldn't radio the ships?
不用,死的!
No, damn it!
我需要爆破筒,火箭筒,迫襞,剪Q……
We need bangalore torpedoes, bazookas, mortars, wire cutters...
……和所有能行拥娜,髟下去行幔
...and every man that can stand. Pass the word, will you?
好的,Z
Okay, Norm.
大家都o我著
Now listen to me, all of you.
你要打起精神
You guys got to snap out of it.
我要x_@向汝前M
We're getting off of here, and we're going inland.
武器呢？④,我的弟兄手o寸F了
What about weapons, general?  My men lost everything.
他得有b洳判
They gotta have something to fight with.
解除死人T的武b
Strip the dead and the wounded.
凡是可用的武器都上
Pick up anything that'll shoot.
用不著我f,你都清楚
I don't have to tell you the score, you all know it.
只有煞N人能留在海┥
Only two kinds of people are gonna stay on this beach:
已死掉的和死掉的,都o我起!
Those that are already dead and those that will die.Get off your butts!
你是身百鸬亩十九!
You guys are the fighting 29th!
我看^海的蟾
I've looked at the naval reports.
怎N樱
Yes?
逐淼蟾嬲f,「WR哈海」炊嗉少
According to reports from the offshore destroyers,Omaha is a shambles.
]有E象……  蟾嬖文是:
There's no evidence--To quote the report exactly:
「海┥嫌^察不到有任何活拥嫩E象」
"There is no evidence of any movement that can be observed off the beach."
我是再看一遍比^好
I'd better have a look through these.
艾克Υ擞泻畏？
How is lke taking it?
和其他人一,L官,在焦急等待
Like everybody else, sir. Hanging on by his fingernails.
不,不!我必照方案六重新部署!
No, no! We must regroup according to Plan Six!
喂？喂？能到幔
Hello? Hello? Can you hear me?
我是f我必照方案六重新部署!
I said we must regroup according to Plan Six.
U!
Nonsense!
如果b甲能磉不算太晚
If the panzers arrive, we still have time to use them.
我乘去海岸!
We'll drive to the coast!
要N文件幔
Shall we remove the files?
@我不在乎!我要R上去前,去Z曼底!
I don't care! I want to get to the front at once, to Normandy!
是,④
Yes, general.
－其他人在哪？－什N？
-Where is everybody?-What?
我f其他人在哪？
I said, where is everybody?
我不
I can't hear you.
是那口大
It's them bells.
在我耳朵Y了足有十^
I've had them in my ears for 10 hours.
叮－,叮－
Ding-dong, ding-dong.
嘿,中士,m斯少校在哪？
Hey, sergeant, where's Major Lance?
指]所D移到了那幢建B,他在那
We moved the CP to that building. The major's there.
去找他,中校砹
Get him, the colonel's here.
什N？
What?
停下!
Hold it!
中校,到你太好了!
Colonel, am I glad to see you!
那些企w,把那些企w弄下
Those bodies. Get those bodies down.
怎N他留在上面？取下!
Why are you leaving them up there?  Get them down!
我一直在火力之下
But we've been under fire, sir.
我知道,但我不管!
I know you have, but I don't care!
快取下!取下!
Get them down! Down!
－我不想弟兄留在那－б魂人去k
-I don't want those boys left there.-Take a detail and cut them down.
－R上去!－是,L官
-At once!-Yes, sir.
我的部和海上的之g有接幔
Has there been a linkup between our forces and the troops from the sea?
不知道,少校,我B他是否已登都不知道
I don't know, major.I don't even know if the landings took place.
我只知道必守住@直到接部前
But I am sure we're gonna hold this town until the linkup does come.
o是今天,明天,是要等到地z鼋Y
Whenever that is, today, tomorrow, till hell freezes over.
哪怕只看在他份上
For their sake, if for no other reason.
告V我橙说奈恢迷谀
Show me the enemy positions.
是,L官,德人的c就在那
Well, sir, the Germans' strong point is right there.
就在那的山上,]有坦克
That's over there on the hill. They've got no tanks yet.
他在公路上方阎昧酥嘏,迫襞诤C
They've got heavy guns, mortars and machine gun positions at the top of that road.
你有多少人？
How many men have you got?
不
Not enough.
上尉和威d中尉В吝B去增援m斯少校
Captain and Lieutenant Wilson will take A Company and reinforce Major Lance.
其他的人跟我一起向公路前M
The rest of the command will follow us straight up that road.
祝你好\,少校
Good luck, major.
好的,ＡB,x
All right, A Company, fall out.
－二等兵
－是,L官
-Private.
-Yes, sir.
真是地z
It's a hell of a war.
我意和您K肩作, 中校
It's a privilege to serve with you, colonel.
但我能完成我泶说哪康
Well, God willing, we'll do what we came here to do.
浜昧,^
Ready, sir.
出l!
Move out!
老^肯定是淖蛱扉_始改的
The old man sure has changed since yesterday.
也可能是我改了……
Or maybe it's just that we've changed...
……淖蛱扉_始
...since yesterday.
拉瓦特已率突絷抵_大
Lovat and his commandos have reached the bridge.
U勃,你在幔
Bob, did you hear?
是的,我在
Yes, I heard.
「}米伊格Y斯已被八十二空降最I」
"Sainte-Mere-Eglise captured by units of the 82nd Airborne."
「一○一空降正在『q他海』推M」
" 101 Airborne driving on Utah."
很好,很好
That's good. Good.
是的,是不e，
但如果不能摹WR哈海」身就毫o意x,@我都清楚
Yes, but if we can't get off Omaha it doesn't mean a damn. We know it.
我拿下了商╊^地,一是英^,一是"q他海"
We'll have two cut-off beachheads,one in British zone and one at Utah.
Yes...
……但是中g是德
...and the Germans in between.
你是工兵幔
You guys engineers?
是,L官,第二九九特N工兵I
Yes, sir, 299th.
指]官呢？@Y由l？
Where are your officers? Who's in charge here?
我想是由我,L官,指]官都不在
I guess I am, sir.  None of our officers made it in.
b淠兀勘破筒能用幔
What about your equipment? Those torpedoes work?
是的,L官,然能用!
Yes, sir, we'll make them work!
－你叫什N,中士？－Ｊ・Ｈ・弗勒,L官
-What's your name, sergeant?-It's Fuller, sir, John H.
F在起你是弗勒少尉,不管你不意
You're Lieutenant Fuller from now on,whether you like it or not.
派人上爆破筒去溪谷底部
You send some men down to the foot of that gully with those torpedoes.
－你和其N的人跟我恚是,L官!
-You and the rest of the men follow me.-Yes, sir!
好了,弟兄!上b潆x_@
All right, men! Let's move that equipment down here.
－我有支,L官－很好,小伙子!
-I got a rifle, sir.-Well, good for you, son!
「pT兵」在待命,L官
The Rangers are ready, general.
好的,少校,叫他出l
Okay, major, move them out.
上尉,他出l
Captain, move them up.
出l!
Move them up!
－什N事？－我浜昧
-Well, Tom?-We're ready.
一切已渚途w
As ready as we'll ever be.
成功的,一定成功
It'll work. It's got to work.
我在@被值!倒不如推M到汝再死!
We're getting murdered here!We might as well move inland and get murdered!
－浜昧耍浚是,L官
-You ready?-Yes, sir.
o我把那路障清除掉
You're gonna blow that roadblock for me.
收到信立刻行,懂幔
When I give the word everything pops at once. Okay?
是,L官
Yes, sir.
我先要用爆破筒在FzW上炸洞
First, we gotta blow a hole through that wire with bangalores.
能成功的就把所有炸填到底下
If that works, we'll pack everything we've got into that wall.
好了,上!
All right, let's go!
行了,n啊!_!_!
All right, let's go! Go! Go!
我必x_,公路志遭到了空u
We must leave. The main highway is under aerial attack.
不用你f!
You don't say!
e心,美佬
Don't worry, Yank.
他死了
He's dead.
o我一支,我想抽想得要命
Give me a cigarette. I'm dying for a cigarette.
得很重幔
You hurt bad?
夜Y被袈淞
Shot down during the night.
他想看我死了]有,被我值袅恕…
He was gonna make sure of me, but I got him...
……用@
...with this.
你⑦^人]有？我是指,面γ娴兀
You ever killed a man? I mean, face to face?
]有
No.
我也]有,面γ娴
Neither had l, face to face.
我一直坐在@看著他
I've been sitting here looking at him.
你lF他有什N特e之]有？
Have you noticed anything peculiar about him?
]有
No.
他的靴子……
He's got his boots...
……穿e了_
...on the wrong feet.
他一定非常匆忙Π桑
He must have been in a big hurry, huh?
乐幔
Is it bad?
裂了大口子……
Split wide open...
……目璨恳恢钡较ドw
...from the crotch to the knee.
有t磉^,o我注射了岱
A medic came along and gave me a shot of morphine.
但他在效失去前回
I hope he'll be back before it wears off.
他f他的
He said he would.
他替你p合]有？
Did he sew you up?
他上岸r把大部分器材都弄G了
Well, when he came ashore he lost most of his equipment.
所以他p合r只能……
So he pinned it together...
……用e
...with safety pins.
天就快黑了
Getting on toward night.
你知道幔
You know something?
我整天都]_^一
I haven't fired my gun all day.
我不嗦到,但每次等我s到,就]人了
I keep hearing shooting,but every time I get there, everybody's gone.
真滑稽,是吧？
Funny, isn't it?
他死了
He's dead.
我瘸了
I'm crippled.
你迷路了
You're lost.
我猜它一直都是@
I suppose it's always like that.
我是指
I mean war.
我想知道lA了
I wonder who won.
好了,送我上山,小伙子
Okay, run me up the hill, son.